Very good morning to everyone. First of all,
many congratulations to your entire team for
becoming number one. And out of my two picks,
my first pick today will be ICICI
Lombard. If you look at the insurance sector as a
whole, then the
price volume action is quite strong in all these stocks.
Whether you look at other insurance stocks as well,
and even in ICC Lombard, the
success of high tops and high bottoms is continuing. So,
here a consolidation phase has already happened last week. So, if
an
up move is expected here, it would be
advisable to buy with a stop loss for targets around 1790.
And my
second pick is Ica Laboratories. So, the
stock has taken a good support around its 89 day 40 day exponential moving average
and from here again positivity is
resuming. So, the
risk to risk ratio is favorable in Ica Laboratories as well. Where it would be
advisable to buy with a stop loss below 1160 for a
short term around 1300.  The
calls for the targets have already appeared on your screen
and now Ashish is placing your two trades.